07901 972 811 contact@rolandlevy.co.uk

Energetic full-stack developer specialising in front-end. Enthusiastic team player and a deep creative thinker with a can-do attitude. Building user-centric, responsive web apps with JavaScript, Vue, React, Node, Express. Keen to learn whatever language or framework it takes to get the job done.

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/roland-levy Portfolio: rolandlevy.co.uk GitHub: github.com/rolandjlevy

Skills

Front-end	Back-end	Tooling / workflow
JavaScript, Vue, React,	Node, Express, EJS,	Git, CLI, Bitbucket, Jest, Enzyme,
Angular, Bootstrap	MySQL, Knex, Php	Webpack, Postman, Jira, Agile

Employment & Experience

Ontrack Management Solutions

Full-stack Developer Feb 2019 - Present

- Working with the Systems Architect, BA, UX / Designer and QA to improve / maintain Ontrack MS*
 which provides end-to-end project, job and task tracking with built-in quality management tools.
- Developing back-end functionality with Node, Express, Knex and EJS. Writing clean, reusable code.
- Building responsive interfaces with Vue.js and some angular.js, Bootstrap, HTML and CSS to meet product and design specifications.
- Learning MVC, OOP, Rest APIs and following principles such as YAGNI, KISS, DRY.
- Conceptualizing, coding, deploying, and iterating on next generation prototypes. Maintaining legacy code and making improvements to increase readability, reliability and reusability.
- Pragmatic approach to analyzing technical issues and clearly communicating solutions.
- *Ontrack MS is used internally so access can be made available upon request.

Constructor Labs

Full-Stack JavaScript bootcamp, Sept – Nov 2018

Built interactive, data-driven web applications over an intensive 12-week programme

- Learned and demonstrated complex concepts within JavaScript, React, Redux, Node and Express
- Developed problem-solving, communication and teamwork skills through pair-programming, agile methodologies and self-directed learning

Here are two example projects:

- Better Change (8-day group project) Cashless payment app that uses QR codes for quick, simple charity donations using React, React Router, Redux, Node, Express, PostgreSQL, SCSS
 Live demo: www.betterchange.net | Github: github.com/Benefit-ConstructorLabs/benefit
- OurBnB (4-day group project) Accommodation booking app using React, Node, Express, Handlebars, PostgreSQL, Grid, Flexbox, Twilio

Live demo: <u>ourbnb.herokuapp.com</u> | Github: <u>github.com/OurBnB/OurBnB</u>

Heruka Kadampa Meditation Centre

Administrative Director March 2014 - April 2018

- Managed events, residential and commercial buildings, residents, finances, operations
- Managed all print and digital marketing campaigns. Trained staff to run them
- Managed the design and development of the website. Self-taught JavaScript, PHP, Wordpress

Education Programme Coordinator (EPC) April 2008 - Feb 2014

- Devised and managed programme of over 30 weekly classes & 15 weekend events annually
- Managed the production and distribution of all digital and printed promotional material
- Gained experience in management, communication, problem solving, teamwork

EPC Assistant Feb 2006 - March 2008

- Managed weekly classes and weekend events. Maintained website: Dreamweaver, HTML and CSS
- Design and production of print design: Photoshop, Indesign, Illustrator

Education

- 12-week full-stack JavaScript bootcamp Constructor Labs
- Diploma in Interactive Multimedia ~ Westminster Kingsway College
- BA Hons Degree in Fine Art, Painting ~ Central Saint Martins College of Art & Design